NIKOLAI MAEV

Senior Software Engineer

trix.mnr@gmail.com — Skype: trix.mnr — Telegram: @trixon — linkedin.com/in/sharpdev/ — nickmaev.github.io

10 years experience in front- and back-end development with a vast array of knowledge in programming languages and tools. Design and development of the SaaP, SaaS practice. Complex problem-solving practice. Good cooperation skills.

Experience

2020-08 -

Current

Full Stack Engineer, ISDK LLC

C#, ASP.NET Core, NodeJS development. Setting up infrastructure using Microsoft Azure. Setting up intra-corporate pipelines using Docker, Linux and Jenkins. Application, database design and development. Front-end design and development with TypeScript, React, Redux. Team management, staff training, code reviewing.

2016-05 -

2020-07

Full Stack Engineer, StecPoint

C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core development. Application, database design and development. Development using microservices. Front-end design and development with TypeScript, React, Redux. Team management, staff training, code reviewing.

2013-07 -

2016-03

Full Stack Developer, S4AB

C#, ASP.NET MVC full-stack development with JavaScript, jQuery. Database design.

Education

2007-09 -

2013-07

The specialist-level degree (eq. to Master's degree) in Radiophysics and electronics, Southern Federal University, Rostov-on-Don

Defending a thesis related to digital signal processing.

Skills

.NET

C#ASP.NET Core

NodeJS

Docker

PostgreSQL

Linux

TypeScript

JavaScript

React

Redux

WebPack

Jenkins

Δ

Azure

xUnitNext.IS

Activities

Creator and main contributor of the several opensource projects which are aimed to construct stable web applications using the most popular programming technologies.

Languages

English B1, Russian C2